<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>MMINDI Connect Santa Fe 2016 Reunion (June 24-26, 2016)</title>
		<description>MMINDI Connect Santa Fe 2016 Reunion site for registration, news, etc.</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Accommodations</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The reunion will be held at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.laposadadesantafe.com&quot;&gt;La Posada De Santa Fe&lt;/a&gt;, a one-of-a-kind resort and spa featuring Pueblo revival architecture.  The resort sits on 6 acres in the heart of downtown Santa Fe, so walking anywhere is truly convenient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently there is a modest block of rooms reserved; however, as reservations are made, the number of rooms will be increased depending on interest in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price of the rooms are $199.00 for a standard, stunning, and $299.00, more stunning, for a suite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The phone number for the hotel and reservations is (505) 986-0000, and the event is under the name Notre Dame International. David says to contact him if there is any confusion - but rather than post his # here, email us &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:mmindiconnect@gmail.com&quot;&gt;mmindiconnect&lt;/a&gt; first we&amp;#39;ll check with him.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>/2016/01/Accomodations</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/01/Accomodations</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Transportation</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Santa Fe is located approximately 1 hour from Albuquerque, New Mexico.  It is also possible to fly into Santa Fe; however, transportation arrangements from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.santafenm.gov/airport&quot;&gt;Santa Fe Airport&lt;/a&gt; should be made ahead of time through the taxi service (505-438-0000).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several car rental options from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abqsunport.com&quot;&gt;Albuquerque Airport&lt;/a&gt; in addition to shuttle services, and if you are adventurous you can take the &lt;a href=&quot;http://riometro.org&quot;&gt;Railrunner&lt;/a&gt;, train, from downtown Albuquerque.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose to take the shuttle, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sandiashuttle.com&quot;&gt;Sandia Shuttle Express&lt;/a&gt; operates from the Albuquerque Airport to Santa Fe throughout the day.  The phone number is (888) 775-5696, and the price is $28.00, one way, and $48.00 for a round trip.  The shuttle will drop you off at the La Posada in Santa Fe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://riometro.org&quot;&gt;The Railrunner&lt;/a&gt; train service runs from Albuquerque to Santa Fe eleven times a day on weekdays*: 4:32 A.M., 5:02 A.M., 6:22 A.M., 7:19 A.M., 8:42 A.M., 9:35 A.M., 4:26 P.M., 5:34 P.M., 6:48 P.M., 7:42 P.M., and 8:38 P.M. The phone number for the Railrunner is (866) 795-RAIL (7245) and the price is $10:00 one-way. If you take the Railrunner you will have to take a cab from the Albuquerque Airport to the downtown train station, which is about 10 to 15 minutes away from the airport.  When you arrive in Santa Fe, you will have to get a cab to La Posada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pricing and schedules are subject to change, they were correct at the time they were investigated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 19:59:59 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>/2016/01/Transportation</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/01/Transportation</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>David Signs Contract</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.laposadadesantafe.com&quot; title=&quot;La Posada De Santa Fe&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/laposadadesantafe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;La Posada De Santa Fe&quot; title=&quot;La Posada De Santa Fe&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David Trujillo, our site host, has secured the wonderful &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.laposadadesantafe.com&quot; title=&quot;La Posada De Santa Fe&quot;&gt;La Posada De Santa Fe&lt;/a&gt;  and signed the contract reserving a block of rooms at a reduced rates. David says on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/1708231322736566/1797044693855228/?comment_id=1803838623175835&amp;amp;notif_t=like&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;The contract is signed. June 24, 25, and 26. Regular room $199 (beautiful by the way) and suites $299. Central location. We can walk to everything. I&amp;#39;m also working on a less pricey option; however, June in santa fe is high season. I&amp;#39;m working on day trips to Bandalier and rafting. Santa Fe is packed with so many options.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/2015/08/David%20Signs%20Contract</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/David%20Signs%20Contract</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>MMINDI Connect Santa Fe 2016 Site is Live</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the MMI NDI Connect Santa Fe 2016 site. This is where you will find all the information regarding the upcoming 2016, June 24-26 Santa Fe Reunion. David Trujillo, NDI &amp;#39;85, is our site host.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several folks behind the scenes who will be involved, and probably don&amp;#39;t even know it yet. ;-) But they will be credited as we move forward!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, if you&amp;#39;re not already aware - there is a large Facebook Contingent of MMI and NDI alumni on Facebook. Contact us here with your name, class year, school, and facebook/email info so we can connect you to the closed group. We might ask you a stupid question to make sure it&amp;#39;s you. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Framework Credit: the original &lt;em&gt;theme&lt;/em&gt; for this site comes from &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/scotte/jekyll-clean&quot;&gt;the original theme on github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 12:25:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/2015/08/MMINDI%20Connect%20Site%20is%20live</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/MMINDI%20Connect%20Site%20is%20live</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
